66.220.18.143 2011-10-07

# QuotesHound :: Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for QuotesHound.com.

### WHO WE ARE AND WHAT WE DO

QuotesHound.com ("Company " or "we" or "our" or "QuotesHound"), owns and operates the website located at www.quoteshound.com, (the "Site"). Through the Site, Company operates a prospective customer data base (the "Service"), by which it compiles, sorts and sells contact information to businesses on behalf of individual consumers who have shown an interest in applying for a business' products or services and has affirmatively asked to be contacted by a representative of a product or service business. Company utilizes third party vendors, third party affiliates, and a variety of media advertisements to promote the Site to consumers interested in completing an online contact request at our Site or to supplement our database by purchasing their database of consumers who have completed applications on websites other than Company's and have affirmatively requested receipt of information about product or service offerings similar to those offered on Company's Site.

###  YOUR PRIVACY IS IMPORTANT TO US

We recognize the importance of protecting your personal information. We collect and retain information about you to communicate with you, to process your requests for products and services, and to inform you about other financial services that may be of interest to you through our news letter. Except as explained here in our Privacy Policy, we do not sell nonpublic personal information about current or former customers, nor do we share this type of information with anyone other than our affiliates. The examples in this Privacy Policy are illustrative only and are not intended to be exclusive.

We want consumers to feel comfortable using the Site and participating in the Service, so we have created this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we may collect from you on the Site and through the Service and how we may use that information. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site and participating in the Service, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site or participate in the Service.

### CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our website only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms and Conditions for more information.

### GENERAL INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

QuotesHound collects information through the Site from our prospective and existing customers at several different points on our web site. We use contact information to send information about our company and to service existing accounts. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Contact and Financial information that is collected is used for verifying your name, address and other information. Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by QuotesHound and may be shared in aggregate with third parties whose services are used for traffic analysis purposes. This information includes: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by QuotesHound to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the QuotesHound site.

### CHOICE/OPT-OUT

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: You can send e-mail to optout@quoteshound.com

Please note that participation in certain activities on our web site may be limited if personally identifiable information is not submitted for the user. E-mail addresses and phone numbers received in an opt-out request will be added to our internal Do-Not-Contact registry within ten (10) Business days following receipt.

### COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site however without cookies the user may not have access to certain features on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. All cookies served on the domain, both session and persistent are tied to the Personally Identifiable Information you provide.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies once set on our site.

### LINKS

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Company even in cases where we may frame another site with our own. From time to time we may co-brand certain services with third parties. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting such information and whose privacy statement governs. For example, without limiting the foregoing, we co-brand with insurance brokers, credit reporting agencies and, automotive companies.

### SECURITY

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When we transmit highly confidential information over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### DISCLOSURE

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances as required by law, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

In addition, as noted above, if you opt-out of future contact from Company by using the opt-out mechanism provided in each e-mail we send to you on behalf of a third party service provider other than Company, we will provide your email address to the third party service provider so that the third party service provider can add your name and contact information to its own do-not-contact list.

As Company develops, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that Company or all of its assets are acquired, customer information, including any visitor information collected through the Site, would be one of the transferred assets. For more information see our "Notification of Changes" section below.

Finally, Company reserves the right to disclose member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) Company's rights or property, other visitors, members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Company also reserves the right to disclose visitor or member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

###  SHARING INFORMATION WITH AFFILIATES

When you submit your request for information or quote, you are granting permission to be contacted by QuotesHound and affiliated third parties. We share the contact and loan request data you submit on the Quote Request form with affiliated companies such as banks, commercial lenders and licensed loan brokers to fulfill information requests we receive from you, to provide you with superior service, inform you of product and service opportunities that may be of interest to you, and for other business purposes may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to the following types of affiliated companies: financial service providers, such as mortgage and life insurance agencies, title service companies, debt & credit services companies and auto finance companies. An "affiliate company" is a company under legal contract with QuotesHound to fulfill services or is a company owned in whole ore in part by QuotesHound.

###  SHARING INFORMATION WITH CO-BRANDED PARTNERS

Some of the services offered on our website are co-branded with contracted partners. Co-Branded offerings will be identified directly on the Quote Request form for the product or service you choose prior to you having to submit the Quote Request. Where a co-branded product or service provider is identified your Personally Identifiable information will be provided directly to that provider's website, not QuotesHound. The Product or Service provider shall control your data once submitted to them. For purposes of identification and tracking, your contact information (name, Address, Phone, e-mail address, etc.) is shared with QuotesHound.

###  CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information against unauthorized access or use. Maintaining the accuracy of your information is a shared responsibility. We maintain the integrity of the information you provide us and will update your records when you notify us of a change. Please contact us at the address or phone number listed below when information concerning you changes.

###  SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES

We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We also communicate with user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via e-mail or telephone when requested.

###  NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will prominently post a notice on the website for 30 days. We may also make a reasonable effort to notify users by way of an e-mail. Users have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this materially different manner.

###  SPECIAL NOTIFICATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Individual customers who reside in California and have provided their personal information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at privacy@quoteshound.com. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year.

### QUESTIONS

Any questions that you may have regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to privacy@quoteshound.com.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on April 30th, 2009
